let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: " common approaches to ethical decision making.",
        answer: "D. All of the above",
        options: [
            "A. virtue ethics approach",
            "B. utilitarian approach",
            "C. fairness approach",
            "D. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: " _____ refers to protecting data and computer system against dishonesty or negligence of employees.",
        answer: "A. Personnel security",
        options: [
            "A. Personnel security",
            "B. Personal security",
            "C. Physical security",
            "D. None of these"
        ]
    },
    { 
        numb: 3,
        question: " types of computer attacks.",
        answer: "D. All of the above",
        options: [
            "A. virus",
            "B. worm",
            "C. Trojan horse",
            "D. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: " Actions taken by Microsoft to support trustworthy computing.",
        answer: "D. All of the above",
        options: [
            "A. Security",
            "B. Privacy",
            "C. Reliability",
            "D. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: " Firewalls can be established through the use of.",
        answer: "C. internal network and the internet",
        options: [
            "A. Internal network",
            "B. the Internet",
            "C. internal network and the internet",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: " You can protect sensitive data from prying eyes using.",
        answer: "A. File permissions",
        options: [
            "A. File permissions",
            "B. File locks",
            "C. Passwords",
            "D. Encryption"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: " Is a set of rules for determining moral standards or socially acceptable behavior.",
        answer: "C. Ethics",
        options: [
            "A. Protocol",
            "B. Standard",
            "C. Ethics",
            "D. None of the given"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: " Cracking‚Äù comes under.",
        answer: "C. Computer Crime",
        options: [
            "A. Website Service",
            "B. Transcription",
            "C. Computer Crime",
            "D. Data Security"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: " A hacker contacts your phone or E-mail and attempts to acquire your password is called.",
        answer: "C. Phishing",
        options: [
            "A. Spamming",
            "B. Spoofing",
            "C. Phishing",
            "D. None of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:10,
        question: " is the illegal access to the network or computer system.",
        answer: "B. Cracking",
        options: [
            "A. Security",
            "B. Cracking",
            "C. Virus",
            "D. Piracy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: " Running other software on idle computer without the knowledge of the organization is called theft of ____.",
        answer: "C. Computer time",
        options: [
            "A. Software",
            "B. Computer",
            "C. Computer time",
            "D. Use"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: " Which of the following is not a way of protection?",
        answer: "C. Piracy",
        options: [
            "A. Physical Security",
            "B. Personal Security",
            "C. Piracy",
            "D. Personnel security"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: " ___ is a self- replicating program that can cause damage to data and files stored on your computer.",
        answer: "A. Virus",
        options: [
            "A. Virus",
            "B. Freeware",
            "C. Piracy",
            "D. None of the given"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: " Making and using duplicate hardware and software is called ___.",
        answer: "A. Piracy",
        options: [
            "A. Piracy",
            "B. Free copy",
            "C. Copy right",
            "D. None of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: " ____ refers to software setups that permit only authorized access to the system.",
        answer: "B. Personal security",
        options: [
            "A. Personnel security",
            "B. Personal security",
            "C. Physical security",
            "D. None of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: " The protection of hardware, facilities magnetic disks, and other illegally accessed, stolen, damaged or destroyed items refers to ____.",
        answer: "A. Physical security",
        options: [
            "A. Physical security",
            "B. Personal security",
            "C. Personnel security",
            "D. None of the given"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: " ________ helps to classify arguments and situations, better understand a cyber-crime and helps to determine appropriate actions.",
        answer: "A. Cyber-ethics",
        options: [
            "A. Cyber-ethics",
            "B. social ethics",
            "C. Cyber-bullying",
            "D. corporate behavior"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: " Which responsibilities fall under professional responsibilities?",
        answer: "D. Above all",
        options: [
            "A. Confidentiality",
            "B. Computer ethics",
            "C. Environmental ethics",
            "D. Above all"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: " Which one does fall under computer ethics?",
        answer: "D. Above all",
        options: [
            "A. Computers can be used for robbery, crime and blackmailing others.",
            "B. Hacking is used to access private information",
            "C. Leak of such information of individual leads to harassments in terms of repeated phone calls",
            "D. Above all"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: " _________ refers to the principles of right and wrong behaviour.",
        answer: "A. Moral",
        options: [
            "A. Moral",
            "B. Oral",
            "C. Coral",
            "D. None"
        ]
    },
];